[Laughter]
come on in
condi slop around I already knew she was
the one that's why I started planning
for us so when I got the message from
Manulife I knew it was time I prepared
everything double-checked triple-checked
back perfectionistic especially since my
gal ko nahin nahin tomorrow near five
years the rain Cassie coming LDR but
she's worth the wait
so I planned the perfect date
first Makita on Big Buddha na pagando
noon tomorrow
rooting around have a fun special rule
book 115 Michele Cammisa how important
sauna 325 satin homage to Star Ferry
that passed before six
data-link wishes a big trap no big crown
but the top was at exactly 6 p.m. we'll
enjoy a romantic date that I've booked
two months ahead
[Music]
now Heineman khmer Sato Sato 9 p.m.
at but man habit number tapas and arrow
you and your name in high in they had no
canonical from the stars would have led
to that
even yet it but it's okay I already
stopped asking what if things don't go
as planned
what if defects are sure what is noble
the whole what is
who you marry me
what if things turn out better than I
planned I said yes
[Music]